Welcome to Pure Love Snack Bar
欢迎来到纯爱小吃店
Little surprises for the girls
给女生的小惊喜
Weng Fanxi said she wanted stir-fried vegetables
翁凡西说她要炒菜
So this is the taste of love
所以这就是爱情的味道
Good work
干得好
They're so adorable together
他们在一起真是太可爱了
Guo Xu is insanely handsome
郭旭真的太帅了
Xiao Enya is also a girl
肖恩雅也是个女孩
There are only three days left of the Tianping Island trip.
距离天平岛之行只剩下三天了。
Suddenly, the sunset of one afternoon
突然，一个下午的夕阳西下
Froze in my mind.
冻结在我的脑海里。
Just today, when I went out and came back,
就在今天，我出去回来后，
It felt like coming home.
感觉就像回家一样。
I’m a little reluctant.
我有点不情愿。
I don’t want to leave either.
我也不想离开。
It hurts inside.
里面很痛。
It's a bit regrettable
是有点遗憾
I think
我认为
I hope after this ends
我希望这一切结束后
I can still be with you
我仍然可以和你在一起
It's not that I don't like him
并不是我不喜欢他
I don't like him
我不喜欢他
I wouldn't have talked with him this long
我不会和他聊这么久
Then there must be some affection
那么一定要有一些感情
Getting closer to going back now
现在离回去越来越近了
Whatever I feel in my heart
无论我心里有什么感觉
That's how I'll act
这就是我将采取的行动
I won't consider anything else anymore
我不会再考虑任何其他事情
Because of my mistake in not choosing her
因为我的错误没有选择她
This is also why I want to fulfill
这也是我想要实现的原因
what I promised her before
我之前答应过她的事
Finally got the chance to go on a date with Fujie
终于有机会和富杰约会了
No matter what
无论
I'll just follow my heart
我只会跟随我的心
Whatever happens, happens
无论发生什么，都会发生
Why haven't you left yet?
你怎么还没走？
You ask me, I ask you.
你问我，我问你。
Go on your date.
去约会吧。
Go on your date already.
已经去约会了。
I'm actually curious where you'll go for fun.
其实我很好奇你会去哪里玩。
She's definitely going to...
她肯定会...
I'm definitely going to the pirate city without rainy days.
没有下雨天我肯定会去海盗城。
She doesn't get my point.
她不明白我的意思。
Playing awkward, huh, Sis?
姐姐玩得很尴尬吧？
Socially dead.
社会死亡。
Didn't you say you were going to play pool?
你不是说要去打台球吗？
I'm telling you, I practically live at that pool hall.
我告诉你，我几乎住在那个台球厅里。
Fellow islanders,
各位岛民们，
Tianping Island's final off-island date is now open.
天平岛最后的离岛日期现已开放。
After last night's invitation choices,
经过昨晚的邀请选择后，
Congratulations to Fu Jie for a successful invitation.
恭喜付洁邀请成功。
Lu Wanfei.
Lu Wanfei.
Invitation successful
邀请成功
Please proceed to the island rendezvous point
请前往岛屿集合点
One at a time
一次一个
Graceful
优美
I must be graceful
我必须优雅
The person I chose for my island date is Lu Wanfei.
我选择的海岛约会对象是陆万菲。
Just like how I initially chose her
就像我当初选择她一样
as my game partner,
作为我的游戏伙伴，
During these final days,
在这最后的日子里，
I feel that currently
我感觉目前
she's still the person I'm most interested in getting to know,
她仍然是我最想认识的人
and the one I've communicated with the most.
也是我交流最多的一个。
So I'm absolutely certain
所以我绝对确定
I'll choose Lu Wanfei.
I'll choose Lu Wanfei.
So handsome today.
今天好帅啊
So handsome.
好帅啊
Fujie is happy again today.
富杰今天又开心了。
When isn't he happy?
他什么时候不高兴？
Goodbye.
再见。
See you later.
稍后见。
Bring us some food, buddies.
朋友们，给我们带点吃的吧。
Okay.
好的。
I want bubble tea.
我想要珍珠奶茶。
One day out and already got a new job.
有一天出去，已经找到了一份新工作。
Became a delivery guy.
成了一名送货员。
Handsome guy and beautiful girl.
英俊的男孩和美丽的女孩。
Goodbye.
再见。
Goodbye, see you tonight.
再见，今晚见。
Okay.
好的。
Remember to come home.
记得回家。
Finally got the chance
终于有机会了
to go on a date with Fujie.
和富杰去约会。
Fujie said he's wearing a white shirt,
富杰说他穿着白衬衫，
so I chose this white dress
所以我选择了这件白色连衣裙
to match with him.
来配合他。
Congratulations to Gu Zhenxiang and Chen Mengjia for successful island date invitations.
恭喜顾振祥、陈梦佳海岛约会邀请成功。
Please proceed to the island meeting point.
请前往岛屿集合点。
Prince, please go on your date.
王子，请去约会吧。
Goodbye.
再见。
Go ahead, off you go.
走吧，你走吧。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Have fun, Gu Zhenxiang.
Have fun, Gu Zhenxiang.
See you tonight.
今晚见。
Left hand hurts.
左手很痛。
Goodbye.
再见。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Have fun.
玩得开心。
Enjoy yourselves.
尽情享受吧。
We'll wait for you to return.
我们会等你回来。
Not coming back, I'm going straight home.
不回来了，我直接回家。
Are you happy?
你快乐吗？
Chinese-style eight-ball
中式八球
I can't wait
我等不及了
Finally got this thing done
终于把这件事搞定了
Right
正确的
Then we need to
那么我们需要
Yeah
是的
Today we're just responsible for having fun
今天我们只负责玩得开心
Exactly
确切地
I think today is definitely
我想今天绝对是
The happiest date ever
有史以来最快乐的约会
Practicing my pool skills in advance
提前练习台球技巧
Don't be so nervous
别那么紧张
I told you I might play terribly
我告诉过你我可能会玩得很糟糕
And what's wrong with losing to me, right?
而且输给我又有什么不好呢，对吧？
I'm so good, "Changsha's best cue"
我太棒了，“长沙最好的球杆”
"Hunan's best cue" and
“湖南最佳球杆”和
"Jiangxi's best cue"
“江西最好的球杆”
Right
正确的
Showdown, ultimate showdown
对决，终极对决
You're my "servant" today
今天你是我的“仆人”
Okay, bro
好的，兄弟
Okay, sis
好的，姐姐
So happy
太高兴了
Going out with my Gu Zhenxiang
和我顾振祥出去玩
The weather is so nice
天气真好
Did you think yesterday I would choose you?
昨天你以为我会选择你吗？
I think
我认为
I think I'd choose
我想我会选择
After being teammates for so long
做了这么久的队友之后
Don't you think I might choose someone else?
你不觉得我可能会选择别人吗？
You'd probably choose Fujie
你可能会选择Fujie
I don't know
我不知道
I don't know either
我也不知道
If we remain teammates from start to finish
如果我们从始至终都是队友
that would be more fulfilling
那会更充实
But let me tell you this
但让我告诉你这一点
If I'm not going out with you
如果我不和你出去
I wouldn't enjoy it
我不会享受它
I understand
我明白
I know how you feel
我知道你的感受
I completely understand
我完全明白
That's hilarious
太搞笑了
Let's just relax today
今天我们就放松一下
Right
正确的
Let's go out together one last time
我们最后一次一起出去吧
Come on, family, gather here
来吧，家人，聚集在这里
Come on, let's talk
来吧，我们来谈谈
Let's make a plan
让我们制定一个计划
Here's the thing
事情是这样的
Yesterday, because Jiang Shangru and I were
昨天因为我和姜尚如
forming alliances
结成联盟
building factions
建立派别
trying to protect Zheng Dedong
trying to protect Zheng Dedong
to give Zheng Dedong a chance to go on a date
给郑德东一个约会的机会
but it backfired
但这适得其反
suddenly all three of us got "eliminated"
突然我们三个人都被“淘汰”了
Zheng Dedong was genuinely unhappy
郑德东真心不高兴
really quite
真的相当
truly upset, he was feeling down
真的很沮丧，他情绪低落
When I asked him, he told me
当我问他时，他告诉我
he felt bad about Weng Fanxi
他对翁凡西感到不好
he thought Weng Fanxi wanted
他以为翁凡西想要
really wanted to go out
真的很想出去
wanted to go out badly, really badly
非常非常非常想出去
but couldn't fulfill this wish
但无法实现这个愿望
He was blaming himself
他在自责
I was wondering if we could today
我想知道我们今天是否可以
create an island date for him
为他创造一个岛屿约会
He's never had a date on the island
他从未在岛上约会过
Well, he has dated
嗯，他已经约会了
but never initiated the invitation himself
但从未亲自发起邀请
Because I think Zheng Dedong is a really great person
因为我觉得郑德东是一个非常伟大的人
Without him, there would be no us
没有他就没有我们
There would be no you
就不会有你
He's a "great matchmaker," he is
他是一位“大媒人”
Without him
没有他
There truly wouldn't be today for me and Xiao Enya
我和萧恩雅真的不会有今天
Because that day he chose Xiao Enya
因为那天他选择了肖恩雅
Xiao Enya chose me
小恩雅选择了我
And that's how we gradually became like this
我们就这样渐渐地变成了这样
So I think
所以我认为
Even yesterday with Jiang Shangru
就连昨天和姜尚如在一起
I said maybe we could give him another one
我说也许我们可以再给他一份
Okay, let's do our best, come on
好吧，我们尽力吧，加油
Come on
快点
Let's go
我们走吧
You know the secret?
你知道这个秘密吗？
Our secret team
我们的秘密团队
Secret team - Operation Date
秘密团队 - 行动日期
Zheng Dedong's Operation Date
Zheng Dedong's Operation Date
Let's go
我们走吧
Okay
好的
Alright, let's go
好吧，我们走吧
Okay, I'll go tell Zheng Dedong first
好的，我先去告诉郑德东
Good luck
祝你好运
Then you get some rest first
那你先休息一下
See you later
稍后见
Zheng Dedong
Zheng Dedong
Let's get to work.
让我们开始工作吧。
Because before Fujie left, he said
因为富杰走之前他说
he wanted to build a small swing for Lu Wanfei.
他想给陆万飞造一个小秋千。
He asked us
他问我们
to get the guys together later
稍后让大家聚在一起
and help him build one.
并帮助他建造一个。
We thought we might
我们以为我们可以
secretly prepare a little surprise for him.
偷偷地给他准备了一个小惊喜。
Right, a swing.
对了，一个秋千。
I think we could do one thing -
我想我们可以做一件事——
we could trick him
我们可以欺骗他
by pretending this is for Fujie.
假装这是给富杰的。
You know what I mean?
你知道我的意思？
A diversion tactic.
一种转移注意力的策略。
Yes, a diversion.
是的，转移注意力。
So you mean Fujie asked you
所以你的意思是富杰问你了
asked us to do this for him,
要求我们为他做这件事，
but he (Zheng Dedong) is actually
但他（郑德东）其实是
in reality
现实中
preparing it for himself.
为自己准备的。
Zheng Dedong, you're going all out.
郑德东，你全力以赴。
I'm such a genius.
我真是个天才。
Let's go, Daniel.
我们走吧，丹尼尔。
Let's go prepare something for Fujie.
我们去给富杰准备点东西吧。
Okay.
好的。
Wait a moment.
稍等。
Let's first determine the height.
我们首先确定高度。
Set the height.
设置高度。
Right, the rope should go above the ladder height.
是的，绳子应该高于梯子的高度。
Hold it steady.
保持稳定。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
Is this okay?
这样可以吗？
Yes.
是的。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Building a swing for Fujie.
为富杰搭建秋千。
Want to be our test subject?
想成为我们的测试对象吗？
Want to be our first test swinger?
想成为我们的第一个测试摇摆者吗？
You can't be the first test swinger.
你不可能是第一个测试摇摆者。
You wouldn't let Zheng Dedong
你不会让郑德东
hang down like this, would you?
像这样垂下来，你愿意吗？
Right.
正确的。
He said
他说
I appeared
我出现了
So are we going to chat with Weng Fanxi now?
那我们现在去跟翁凡西聊天吗？
No, you go first.
不，你先走。
You go chat with the girls over there for now.
你先去和那边的女孩们聊天吧。
You keep them talking while we tie this up.
在我们解决这个问题的时候，你让他们继续说话。
Then keep it quiet.
然后保持安静。
Don't be so obvious, "Big Blabbermouth."
别表现得那么明显，“大嘴巴”。
How's it going?
怎么样了？
More or less.
或多或少。
Just barely managing to wobble along is fine.
只要勉强能摇摇晃晃就可以了。
Tie it.
系紧它。
It's tied.
是绑着的。
With these conditions, don't expect anything fancy.
有了这些条件，就不要指望有什么奇特的东西了。
If Fu Jie isn't satisfied, let him go home.
付洁不满意就让他回家吧。
Stop making such a fuss.
别这么大惊小怪了。
I'm exhausted, Jiang Shangru.
我累了，姜尚如。
Fu Jie is so annoying.
Fu Jie is so annoying.
Do you know what he's doing now?
你知道他现在在做什么吗？
He's sneezing like crazy.
他疯狂地打喷嚏。
Okay.
好的。
Thanks for your hard work.
感谢您的辛勤工作。
No problem.
没问题。
Overall, it's perfect.
总的来说，它是完美的。
This swing...
这个秋千...
Fu Jie owes us a meal.
付洁欠我们一顿饭。
Two meals.
两顿饭。
Right.
正确的。
I think it's quite nice.
我认为这非常好。
What else do we need to set up next?
接下来我们还需要设置什么？
There seems to be another dating spot.
似乎还有另一个约会地点。
Because right now it's just a recreational facility.
因为现在它只是一个娱乐设施。
Alright.
好吧。
The items are prepared in the storage room.
物品已在储藏室准备好。
We'll move them over bit by bit.
我们会把它们一点一点地移过去。
Okay.
好的。
Maybe we'll arrange a simple Western meal for him.
也许我们可以为他安排一顿简单的西餐。
And then...
进而...
Music, we need music.
音乐，我们需要音乐。
Absolutely.
绝对地。
I made a wish yesterday.
我昨天许了愿。
Yes, absolutely.
是的，绝对是。
Bluetooth speaker is ready.
蓝牙音箱已准备就绪。
Then get some "red water."
然后喝点“红水”。
"Little red water."
“小红水。”
Fine.
美好的。
Full of ceremony.
充满仪式感。
Full blast.
全面爆发。
So meticulous, Fu Jie.
So meticulous, Fu Jie.
Suddenly showing his delicate side (a rough exterior with a fine interior).
突然展现出他细腻的一面（外表粗糙，内心细腻）。
Why did you change your clothes?
你为什么换衣服？
Yeah.
是的。
Helping Fu Jie with something.
帮付洁做事。
And I made you a cup of coffee.
我给你泡了一杯咖啡。
But hasn't Fu Jie already gone out?
可是付洁不是已经出去了吗？
Why are you helping Fu Jie?
你为什么要帮付洁？
He said he wanted to set up a swing.
他说他想搭个秋千。
Said Fu Jie would be back tonight.
说付洁今晚就回来。
Wants to swing with Lu Wanfei.
想和陆婉菲一起荡秋千。
Really? Fu Jie is such a romantic.
真的吗？付洁真是个浪漫的人。
"Zhang Fei doing embroidery" (rough exterior but careful inside).
“张飞绣花”（外表粗犷，内心细致）。
We'll play basketball later.
稍后我们会打篮球。
Later then.
稍后。
We'll see later.
我们稍后会看到。
Let's organize a basketball game this afternoon.
今天下午我们组织一场篮球比赛吧。
Because Zheng Dedong is good at basketball.
因为郑德东擅长篮球。
He plays basketball really well.
他篮球打得非常好。
I think he shows his charm on the court.
我认为他在球场上展现了他的魅力。
So what we girls need to do.
那么我们女孩子需要做什么。
Is to get Weng Fanxi to watch the game.
就是为了让翁凡西去看比赛。
And cheer for him.
并为他加油。
Go Zheng Dedong!
Go Zheng Dedong!
Okay.
好的。
Come help me change shoes, let's go.
来帮我换鞋吧，走吧。
Let's go, I'll go with you to change shoes.
走吧，我陪你去换鞋。
Is Fu Jie really that romantic?
付洁真有那么浪漫吗？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Tao Zhi.
Tao Zhi.
Hello.
你好。
What are you guys doing?
你们在做什么？
We're going to play ball.
我们要去打球。
Going to play ball, want to come?
要去打球，你要来吗？
So boring, let's go.
太无聊了，走吧。
Let's go play ball.
我们去打球吧。
Is Hu Wei sleeping?
胡伟睡觉了吗？
Yes, go call her.
是的，去给她打电话。
She's been sleeping for so long.
她已经睡了这么久了。
Hu Wei.
Hu Wei.
You okay?
你还好吗？
Sleeping soundly
睡得很香
You're really sleeping soundly
你真的睡得很香
We're going to play basketball
我们要去打篮球
We're going to...
我们要去...
Okay
好的
Then I'm coming
那我来了
Let's go
我们走吧
Sorry
对不起
So cute
太可爱了
Waiting for you
等着你
What were you guys doing just now?
你们刚才在做什么？
Fu Jie really wants to swing, going all out
付洁真想摇摆，全力以赴
Yes
是的
Took a while to tie it, it was pretty tricky
花了点时间才打结，好麻烦
Then they'll come back at night and just sit there
然后他们会在晚上回来坐在那里
Probably
大概
A perfect day for them
对他们来说是完美的一天
So awesome, so envious
太厉害了，太羡慕了
Hello
你好
Come on
快点
Weng Fanxi is here
Weng Fanxi is here
Weng Fanxi, have you seen guys play basketball?
翁凡西，你见过男人打篮球吗？
What's so interesting about that?
这有什么有趣的？
Zheng Dedong plays really well
郑德东演得真好
Messing with my head, on purpose
故意搞乱我的头
Really funny
真的很有趣
Do you want to join?
你想加入吗？
You play with Weng Fanxi
你跟翁凡熙玩
Let me see if we can switch
让我看看我们是否可以切换
Daniel, come up here and set a pick for me
丹尼尔，过来帮我选一个
Can fight solo
可以单打独斗
No defense
无防御
Okay
好的
Very cool
非常酷
Let's begin
让我们开始吧
You know what, I'll keep passing to him
你知道吗，我会继续传球给他
Break through inside
突破内部
I'll create space for you
我会为你创造空间
I'm the pitcher
我是投手
Nice shot
好球
Great shot
很棒的镜头
Zheng Dedong
Zheng Dedong
Substitution
替代
Zheng Dedong is super handsome
Zheng Dedong is super handsome
The rhythm is off
节奏没了
How embarrassing to get hit on the head
头被撞了多尴尬
Have you lost your composure, Guo Xu?
郭旭你失态了吗？
Tell me, have you really lost your composure?
告诉我，你真的失去了冷静吗？
Defeated my teammates
打败了我的队友
Breakthrough
突破
Don't listen to him
别听他的
So cool
太酷了
Nice shot
好球
Great shot
很棒的镜头
Well played
打的好
Excellent move
出色的举动
They're all really skilled
他们都非常熟练
Who do you think is the best?
你认为谁是最好的？
Zheng Dedong
Zheng Dedong
Actually Zheng Dedong got nervous after you arrived
其实你来了之后郑德东就紧张了
Before you came, he kept shooting three-pointers
你来之前，他一直在投三分球
I could tell from his expression
从他的表情我可以看出
Would you like some water?
您想要一些水吗？
I'm a little thirsty.
我有点渴了。
Coffee Dream Factory
咖啡梦工厂
I want to sit on the left.
我想坐左边。
Okay
好的
There's coffee
有咖啡
These are all my favorites
这些都是我的最爱
Let's have some coffee first
我们先喝点咖啡吧
Here
这里
Thank you
谢谢
Give me yours
给我你的
What's wrong?
怎么了？
You spilled it on your skirt.
你把它洒在裙子上了。
It's nothing.
没什么。
I'll go wash it off later.
稍后我去洗掉。
To the bathroom.
到浴室。
It should come off.
它应该脱落。
I'm just this messy.
我就是这么乱。
I'm always like this
我总是这样
I usually get my clothes all dirty while eating
我吃饭时经常把衣服弄脏
It's fine
没关系
We'll deal with it later
我们稍后再处理
No problem
没问题
I think so too
我也这么认为
Can we ask some questions?
我们可以问一些问题吗？
What kind of questions?
什么样的问题？
About your profession—I'm really curious.
关于你的职业——我真的很好奇。
I'm genuinely curious.
我真的很好奇。
So, do you own a gym?
那么，你有健身房吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Actually, I do have my own gym.
事实上，我确实有自己的健身房。
And then?
进而？
Really?
真的吗？
No, just kidding.
不，只是开玩笑。
You give off finance or lawyer vibes.
你散发出金融或律师的气息。
Or maybe something in tech.
或者也许是科技方面的东西。
I think it's one of these three
我认为这是这三个之一
Among the three you just mentioned
你刚才提到的这三个中
one guess was correct
一个猜测是正确的
It's the internet industry
这是互联网行业
I'm a database engineer
我是一名数据库工程师
So
所以
You're a database engineer?
你是数据库工程师？
Yes
是的
Do you work with relational database systems or...
您使用关系数据库系统还是......
Yes, we work with relational ones
是的，我们与有关系的人合作
So you specialize in relational databases
所以你专注于关系数据库
Right, we use a different product
是的，我们使用不同的产品
Honestly, I'm surprised you
老实说，我很惊讶你
How do you know about this?
你怎么知道这件事？
Have you also
你是否也
I've studied a database project before
我之前研究过一个数据库项目
So it's actually quite challenging
所以这实际上是很有挑战性的
It's not too bad
还不错
I've just been doing it for many years
我已经这样做很多年了
You're full of surprises
你充满了惊喜
You look like someone who...
你看起来像一个...
(I'm about to offend people again)
（又要得罪人了）
Never mind, I won't say it
没关系，我不会说
But I really want to say
但我真的很想说
With all that hair
有了那么多头发
And such a great figure
还有这么棒的身材
You're actually a programmer?
你真的是程序员吗？
That's why I think
这就是为什么我认为
This is what I appreciate about joining this show
这就是我对参加这个节目的感激之情
It makes me appreciate
这让我很欣赏
Not having too many labels
没有太多的标签
Setting aside these stereotypes
抛开这些刻板印象
Actually, everyone
其实大家
Can completely surprise you
完全可以让你大吃一惊
But you're exceptionally unexpected
但你却出乎意料
I think you're a very profound person.
我觉得你是一个很有深度的人。
I mean, I think a muscular guy...
我的意思是，我认为一个肌肉男...
can't completely define who you are.
无法完全定义你是谁。
It makes you seem quite mysterious to me.
这让我觉得你很神秘。
There's a strong contrast between your inner and outer self.
你的内在自我和外在自我之间存在着强烈的对比。
Outwardly very tough...
外表上非常坚韧...
but inwardly very soft and delicate.
但内心却非常柔软和细腻。
And you're the most fit programmer I've ever seen.
而且你是我见过的最合适的程序员。
Such a perfect physique...
如此完美的身材...
combined with such a brilliant mind.
加上如此聪明的头脑。
You're pretty much the perfect man.
你几乎是一个完美的男人。
So I think...
所以我认为...
you seem to fulfill all...
你似乎满足了所有...
my fantasies about an ideal partner.
我对理想伴侣的幻想。
So I think it's really great.
所以我认为这真的很棒。
What about you?
你呢？
Your turn now.
现在轮到你了。
Guess what I do.
猜猜我做什么。
What do I look like I do?
我看起来像什么？
You look like a model, right?
你看起来像个模特，对吧？
Probably.
大概。
Yes, you look like a fitness trainer.
是的，你看起来像一个健身教练。
Right.
正确的。
I've always thought...
我一直以为...
from the first day I saw you...
从我见到你的第一天起...
first, you're very tall, right?
首先，你很高，对吧？
And your appearance is outstanding.
而且你的外表也很出众。
I thought you probably...
我以为你可能...
use these advantages in your...
利用这些优势在您的...
work.
工作。
your profession.
你的职业。
But at the same time I feel...
但同时我又觉得...
you're a very smart person.
你是一个非常聪明的人。
And talking with you...
并与你交谈...
makes me feel you're actually very driven.
让我觉得你实际上很有动力。
Very competitive.
非常有竞争力。
So that would be finance.
这就是金融。
I think you might have that kind of vibe.
我想你可能也有这样的气质。
Yes, I work in finance.
是的，我从事金融工作。
I do primary investments.
我做初级投资。
It's a direction I'm completely unfamiliar with.
这是一个我完全陌生的方向。
Really.
真的。
But why do I...
但为什么我...
have this very superficial understanding of it?
有这样很肤浅的认识吗？
About you.
关于你。
So you're just lowering your standards for me?
所以你只是降低了对我的标准？
No.
不。
That's not what I meant.
我不是这个意思。
I think it's fate.
我想这就是命运。
I was a little surprised.
我有点惊讶。
At the same time, I think she's intelligent,
同时我觉得她很聪明
and also has a very attractive appearance.
并且还具有非常吸引人的外观。
That's definitely a plus.
这绝对是一个优点。
So where do you usually live?
那么你通常住在哪里？
I live in Singapore.
我住在新加坡。
Then we're still quite far apart.
那么我们的距离还是很远的。
Yes.
是的。
I'm quite distant from
我距离很远
most people here.
这里的大多数人。
How long is the flight from Singapore to Beijing?
从新加坡飞往北京需要多长时间？
Never flown before.
以前没飞过。
I think it takes at least four or five hours.
我想至少需要四五个小时。
Haven't you flown to Beijing before?
你以前没有飞过北京吗？
No.
不。
What about business trips?
商务旅行呢？
Sometimes.
有时。
I don't go on business trips.
我不去出差。
Because most of our work
因为我们的大部分工作
can be done
可以做到
online.
在线的。
My mind went blank.
我的脑子一片空白。
It's just the initial stage of having a crush
这只是暗恋的初级阶段
I just feel that such a long distance
我只是觉得这么远的距离
really makes me conflicted
真的让我很矛盾
makes me overthink things
让我想太多
Let's have pizza, I'll cut it for you
我们吃披萨吧，我给你切它
Okay
好的
I went to Singapore in 2015
我2015年去过新加坡
Did you like it?
你喜欢它吗？
Yes
是的
I like warm places
我喜欢温暖的地方
That's why my English name is Summer
这就是为什么我的英文名字是Summer
Summer is my favorite season
夏天是我最喜欢的季节
And Singapore is a place
新加坡是一个地方
of eternal summer
永恒的夏天
A place of endless summer
一个拥有无尽夏日的地方
I'm curious why you chose to live in Singapore
我很好奇你为什么选择住在新加坡
Because I also love summer
因为我也喜欢夏天
Summer is my favorite season
夏天是我最喜欢的季节
That's why my English name is Summer
这就是为什么我的英文名字是Summer
Okay
好的
Really
真的
You're afraid of the cold
你怕冷
You're also afraid of the cold
你也怕冷
I'm not afraid of the cold
我不怕冷
But that doesn't stop me from liking summer
但这并不妨碍我喜欢夏天
What are you trying to say?
你想说什么？
Don't be shy
不要害羞
I don't know why
我不知道为什么
I feel a bit shy when I'm with you
和你在一起时我感到有点害羞
I
我
Usually don't have a shy personality
通常没有害羞的性格
Really?
真的吗？
Are you serious?
你是认真的？
Really
真的
That day when we played games together
那天我们一起打游戏
Do you remember?
你是否记得？
That day when you said those things next to me
那天你在我旁边说那些话
What did I say?
我说什么了？
Our first time staying on the island
我们第一次住在岛上
I wasn't myself the entire day
我一整天都不是我自己
It was like I realized for the first time in my life
这就像我有生以来第一次意识到
That I could actually feel shy
我真的会感到害羞
We'll always be together, right?
我们会永远在一起的，对吧？
I felt shy all day long
我一整天都感到害羞
There were times I didn't dare look at you
有时候我不敢看你
Perhaps that day I spoke to you more than usual
也许那天我对你说的比平常多
And in front of all the guests
并且当着所有来宾的面
I made some
我做了一些
rather pointed choices
相当尖锐的选择
Because in the first half of our time together
因为我们在一起的前半段时间
I was in a state where
我当时的状态是
I hadn't clearly expressed
我没有明确表达
interest in anyone
对任何人感兴趣
So what I did that day
所以那天我做了什么
For me
为我
was quite a breakthrough
是一个很大的突破
During the games that day
当天比赛期间
Why didn't you
你为什么不
Weng Fanqian has a great personality too
翁凡谦也很有个性
Why didn't you approach Weng Fanqian
你为什么不去找翁凡谦
Because at that time
因为当时
Actually, Weng Fanxi
Actually, Weng Fanxi
was also quite close with Zheng Dedong
和郑德东也颇有缘分
I think it would
我认为会
somewhat
有些
possibly lead to some misunderstandings
可能会导致一些误会
Moreover, Zheng Dedong is also my good friend
而且，郑德东也是我的好朋友
I think during that entire event
我认为在整个事件期间
he might choose Weng Fanxi, so
he might choose Weng Fanxi, so
Let me ask you a question
让我问你一个问题
If it weren't for Zheng Dedong
如果不是郑德东
would you have spent time and effort
你会花时间和精力吗
to get close to Weng Fanxi?
接近翁凡西？
I think
我认为
it wasn’t entirely because
这并不完全是因为
of Zheng Dedong
of Zheng Dedong
After interacting with both of you
与双方互动后
for a while
一阵子
I might have
我可能有
already developed
已经开发了
a certain preference
某种偏好
Yeah
是的
I feel like
我觉得
especially that night
尤其是那天晚上
after comforting Chen Mengjia
after comforting Chen Mengjia
you were visibly upset waiting there
你在那里等待显然很不高兴
as if you were waiting for me
就像你在等我一样
it genuinely moved me
这真的让我感动
Lu Wanfei
Lu Wanfei
Do you want to go find her?
你想去找她吗？
What’s wrong?
怎么了？
I don’t know
我不知道
You wear your emotions on your sleeve
你把你的情绪表露在袖子上
Really?
真的吗？
It makes you more approachable
它让你更加平易近人
Like a child
像个孩子一样
I’d say "adorable"
我会说“可爱”
I think "adorable" is the highest praise
我认为“可爱”是最高的评价
Yeah, you get it
是的，你明白了
I genuinely find her adorable
我真的觉得她很可爱
Right
正确的
And then
进而
Even in front of everyone
甚至当着所有人的面
you’d still show
你仍然会表现出
that kind of affection toward me
对我的那种感情
It made me feel you weren’t hiding anything
这让我觉得你没有隐瞒任何事情
That’s why this feeling I have for you
这就是为什么我对你有这种感觉
feels even more real
感觉更加真实
So at that moment
所以那一刻
I really had
我真的有过
already made up my mind
我已经下定决心了
in my heart
在我心里
I just didn’t want to say it
我只是不想说
because I felt
因为我觉得
I might not be entirely sure
我可能不完全确定
I was actually quite curious
我其实很好奇
about what was on your mind during those days
那些日子里你的想法
I felt you had this kind of
我感觉你有这样的
ability to calm me down instantly
让我立刻平静下来的能力
Just being by your side
只要在你身边
made me feel exceptionally
让我感觉异常
peaceful inside
内心平静
exceptionally calm
异常平静
and completely at ease
并完全放心
So I began consciously paying attention to you
于是我开始有意识地关注你
observing you
观察你
when you would be happy
当你会幸福的时候
what things would upset you
什么事情会让你心烦意乱
who your eyes would look at
你的眼睛会看着谁
When I was in a bad mood
当我心情不好的时候
whether you noticed or not
无论你是否注意到
all of these things
所有这些事情
were quite important to me
对我来说非常重要
Then
然后
Right, I need a moment to recover.
好吧，我需要一点时间恢复一下。
I think
我认为
Maybe by asking this
也许通过问这个
I might be putting too much pressure on you
我可能给你太大的压力
If you feel
如果你觉得
I don't
我不
I'm just speaking from the heart
我只是发自内心地说
Because I feel the pressure of survival
因为我感受到了生存的压力
Humans are truly fragile
人类确实很脆弱
And then
进而
I feel like I gave all of
我感觉我付出了所有
my attention on this island
我对这个岛的关注
completely to you
完全给你
But I don't feel that
但我不这么觉得
you gave all of your attention
你付出了全部的注意力
to me
大部头书
to everyone else
给其他人
I don't think you firmly
我不认为你坚定
chose me
选择了我
This makes me feel a little hurt
这让我感到有点受伤
For me personally,
就我个人而言，
I've always felt that these
我一直觉得这些
rather obvious preferential actions
比较明显的优惠动作
might require more time to consider carefully
可能需要更多时间仔细考虑
and make your decision properly.
并做出正确的决定。
You shouldn't go back and forth,
你不应该来回走动
because if you make the wrong choice in such matters,
因为如果你在这些事情上做出了错误的选择，
I think withdrawing or even changing your mind
我认为撤回甚至改变主意
would cause even greater hurt.
会造成更大的伤害。
That's why I've been reluctant
这就是我一直不情愿的原因
when I myself haven't
当我自己还没有
gotten to know you well enough
足够了解你了
to do this.
来做到这一点。
You're someone who takes time to warm up,
你是一个需要时间热身的人
I can understand that.
我能理解。
Anyway, it wasn't until later when we
无论如何，直到后来我们
played more games together,
一起玩更多的游戏，
sat together more on that beach bench,
更多地一起坐在沙滩长椅上，
spent more time together,
花更多的时间在一起，
had more conversations,
进行了更多的交谈，
took more walks together...
一起多散步...
Do you think we have similarities?
你觉得我们有相似之处吗？
We both enjoy watching sunsets.
我们都喜欢看日落。
I confirmed my feelings,
我确认了我的感受
that I have feelings for you.
我对你有感觉。
At least I've clarified my own thoughts,
至少我已经明确了自己的想法
and I feel completely at ease now.
我现在感觉完全放松了。
So I'm very happy.
所以我很高兴。
Do you want me to pull you up?
要我拉你上来吗？
Between the two of us,
我们两个人之间，
there is some mutual attraction.
有一定的相互吸引力。
Just slowly appreciating the sunset together
就这样一起慢慢欣赏日落
is enough to become one of my most
就足以成为我最喜欢的人之一
precious memories on this island.
在这个岛上留下的珍贵回忆。
I feel like I'm gradually adding more
我感觉我正在逐渐添加更多
weight to this preference.
对此偏好的权重。
This might be an answer I find convincing now
这可能是我现在认为有说服力的答案
The time to reveal it
是时候揭晓了
My belly's sticking out
我的肚子突出了
Help me
帮我
I feel like I ate three days' worth of island food
我感觉我吃了三天的岛上食物
Go straight, bro
直走吧兄弟
Okay
好的
Who are you calling "bro"?
你叫谁“兄弟”？
I'm calling you "bro"
我叫你“兄弟”
Don't hit me
别打我
I'll "kill" you
我会“杀掉”你
I can't stand you anymore
我再也无法忍受你了
Let's play pool!
我们来打台球吧！
Let's go!
我们走吧！
Let's have a penalty for each round, okay?
让我们每轮都有一个惩罚，好吗？
Okay.
好的。
You start.
你开始吧。
Let me see your skills.
让我看看你的技能。
Okay
好的
Won't leave
不会离开
No strength
没有力气
Haven't eaten
没吃过
Let me make
让我做
Half and half
一半一半
Why did you suddenly laugh?
怎么突然笑了？
I think I understand now.
我想我现在明白了。
I think I get it.
我想我明白了。
Are you really that skilled?
你真的有那么熟练吗？
I know you must be really impressive.
我知道你一定很令人印象深刻。
"Jiangxi's Best Cue"
“江西最佳球杆”
Not at all.
一点也不。
Is nothing compared to you.
与你相比，根本不算什么。
Amazing.
惊人的。
What
什么
What is this thing
这是什么东西
It's charm
这就是魅力
This is the fourth one
这是第四个
This one is heavy
这个很重
Let me think
让我想想
Good, well said.
好，说得好。
Freedom, huh?
自由吧？
Right.
正确的。
Slams the table.
拍桌子。
The freedom you wanted.
你想要的自由。
This boasting has gone too far.
这种自夸太过分了。
You're nothing in front of her.
你在她面前什么都不是。
She's truly amazing.
她真的很了不起。
Didn't expect that.
没想到会这样。
Why has "Jiangxi's Best" lost his confidence?
“江西最佳”为何失去信心？
"Jiangxi's Best."
"Jiangxi's Best."
"Jiangxi's Ten-thousandth Best."
“江西万佳”。
No.
不。
Didn't expect you to be this good.
没想到你这么好。
First question.
第一个问题。
Who do you think you'd date on the island.
你认为你会在岛上和谁约会？
A girl, would make you happiest.
一个女孩，会让你最幸福。
Is that even a question?
这还是一个问题吗？
Who?
WHO？
Who makes you happiest.
谁让你最幸福。
Most relaxed with.
最轻松的搭配。
Okay.
好的。
You're killing me with laughter
你笑死我了
Seriously
严重地
That's way too much bragging
这实在是太过于自夸了
I feel more relaxed with Chen Mengjia
和陈梦佳在一起我感觉轻松多了
Actually when I'm with her
其实当我和她在一起的时候
We can do many things without feeling awkward
我们可以做很多事情而不会感到尴尬
Everything feels comfortable
一切都感觉很舒服
Because I'm most relaxed when with her
因为和她在一起我最放松
I don't have any inhibitions
我没有任何抑制
That's true
这是真的
Not fair
不公平
I lost
我输了
So which will you choose?
那么你会选择哪一个呢？
Truth or dare
真心话还是大冒险
Go wild
狂野起来
Let loose, don't care
放开，不在乎
Okay then do a solo dance
好吧，那就来一段独舞吧
It's time to show your charm.
是时候展现你的魅力了。
Just dance here for one minute.
在这里跳舞一分钟。
Not too much.
不是太多。
You said yourself anything goes.
你自己也说过，什么事都会发生。
You're such a "dog."
你真是一条“狗”。
There's no music.
没有音乐。
Hurry up and dance.
快点跳舞吧。
Make your own music.
制作你自己的音乐。
Boss, play some music for me.
老板，给我放点音乐吧。
I can't take it anymore
我再也受不了了
Then I'll dance the same one Wei performed last time
那我就跳上次小薇跳的那支舞
Okay?
好的？
Come on, Gu Zhenxiang
Come on, Gu Zhenxiang
Go for it
大胆试试吧
Sure, versatile.
当然，多才多艺。
Together.
一起。
Okay.
好的。
We're ready.
我们准备好了。
We can wrap it up.
我们可以把它包起来。
Come on, let's do it.
来吧，我们开始吧。
Just move a little.
只要稍微动一下。
Come here.
过来吧。
Like this?
像这样？
Is this right?
这是对的吗？
Gu Zhenxiang and I are two childish "ghosts."
我和顾振祥是两个幼稚的“幽灵”。
I'm naturally quite childish.
我天生就很孩子气。
And he's also very adorable.
而且他也很可爱。
He has his own carefree and childlike innocence.
他有自己的无忧无虑和童心。
The atmosphere is especially joyful and relaxed.
气氛特别欢乐、轻松。
Lean back a bit.
向后倾斜一点。
Okay
好的
This is my punishment
这是我的惩罚
I'm not punishing you
我不是在惩罚你
You're punishing me
你在惩罚我
Listen
听
Let's talk about the punishment first, okay?
我们先来说说处罚吧？
Your punishment is
你的惩罚是
to sing a song in public
在公共场合唱歌
Okay
好的
You don't have to sing the whole song
你不必唱整首歌
What song should I sing?
我应该唱什么歌？
Sing a romantic love song
唱一首浪漫的情歌
Alright
好吧
Sing it to me, okay?
唱给我听，好吗？
You're drenched in sweat, little bro.
小兄弟，你已经被汗湿透了。
Just sing a few lines then.
那就唱几句吧。
If those two...
如果那两个...
You
你
I can't take it anymore
我再也受不了了
I'll hold back, you sing
我会忍住，你唱歌
"Help"
“帮助”
Come on
快点
Quick
快的
"Help"
“帮助”
Come on
快点
Quick
快的
I won't look at you
我不会看你
You sing
你唱歌
I can't remember the tune
我不记得曲子了
You know
你知道
Ten years ago
十年前
I didn't know you
我不认识你
You didn't belong to me
你不属于我
We were still the same
我们还是一样
Gu Zhenxiang performed many talents
顾振祥表演多才多艺
And also sang songs
还唱起了歌
And danced too
还跳舞了
I thought it was really fun
我觉得这真的很有趣
Really adorable
真可爱
This was my first time singing on camera
这是我第一次在镜头前唱歌
I thought it was very romantic
我觉得这很浪漫
And also very interesting
而且也非常有趣
Let's leave it at that
我们就这样吧
Alright
好吧
Okay
好的
How about this
这个怎么样
If you score a goal
如果你进球了
you can punish me once
你可以惩罚我一次
Punish me once, right?
惩罚我一次吧？
Yes
是的
Okay
好的
If I score a goal, I'll punish you once
如果我进球了，我就惩罚你一次
Alright, go ahead and ask
好吧，继续问吧
Did you ever think about changing teammates midway?
有没有想过中途更换队友？
Actually, I did consider changing teammates
其实我确实考虑过换队友
But I feel we have better chemistry together
但我觉得我们在一起有更好的化学反应
And it's easier to win some matches together
一起赢得一些比赛会更容易
What was the reason for changing teammates?
更换队友的原因是什么？
I just felt
我只是觉得
that I could also get to know
我也可以了解
some other girls
其他一些女孩
Because I barely had
因为我几乎没有
any interaction with them
与他们的任何互动
Then let me ask you
那我问你
Who do you think are
你认为是谁
the top three girls you like
你喜欢的前三名女孩
on Tianping Island?
在天平岛上？
Then I'll talk about the ones I have a crush on.
那我就来说说我喜欢的人吧。
Is that okay?
可以吗？
Of course, the three I have feelings for.
当然，我对这三个人都有感情。
I have a crush on them.
我迷恋他们。
It's you
是你
No particular order
无特定顺序
No ranking
无排名
Hu Wei, you
Hu Wei, you
And Chen Menger
还有陈梦儿
Just said there's no order
刚刚说没有订单
Then changed the sequence
然后改变了顺序
It's you
是你
No priority
无优先权
Hu Wei, you
Hu Wei, you
Men
男士
You should rank them too
你也应该对它们进行排名
Not three people
不是三个人
Only you
只有你
Not three, just you
不是三个，只有你
Sis has good taste in men
姐姐对男人的品味很好
Gu Zhenxiang
Gu Zhenxiang
Being liked
被喜欢
I don't think it's a bad thing
我不认为这是一件坏事
Right?
正确的？
And there's no need to feel pressured
并且没有必要感到压力
But I think
但我认为
We have such great fun together, don't we?
我们在一起玩得很开心，不是吗？
When I express this fondness
当我表达这份喜爱之情时
It doesn't mean I want to date you or anything
这并不意味着我想和你约会或者其他什么
It's just my way of showing appreciation
这只是我表达感激之情的方式
Yes, I feel the same
是的，我也有同样的感觉
That's exactly how I feel too
我也这么觉得
So you don't need to give me
所以你不需要给我
any "rejection cards"
任何“拒绝卡”
Cheers
干杯
How about singing another song?
唱另一首歌怎么样？
Still want to sing?
还想唱歌吗？
Yeah
是的
You sing one
你唱一首
I told all the lies
我说了所有的谎言
You believed them all
你全都相信了
The simple "I love you"
简单的“我爱你”
You never seem to believe
你似乎从来不相信
We
我们
have just experienced an exhilarating basketball game.
刚刚经历了一场激动人心的篮球比赛。
Yes,
是的，
congratulations to our winner,
祝贺我们的获胜者，
Zheng Dedong.
Zheng Dedong.
Zheng Dedong,
Zheng Dedong,
the MVP of the winning team.
获胜球队的 MVP。
Zheng Dedong, please step forward.
郑德东，请上前。
What's this about?
这是关于什么的？
Now,
现在，
don't do anything reckless.
不要鲁莽行事。
On behalf of Tianping Island, I declare
我代表天平岛声明
that...
那...
Congratulations to Zheng Dedong for winning a
恭喜郑德东荣获
dating opportunity on the island
岛上约会的机会
You can invite the female guest who caught your eye
您可以邀请您感兴趣的女嘉宾
Ask if she's willing to go with you
询问她是否愿意和你一起去
on this date
在这个日期
Okay
好的
Let's begin
让我们开始吧
Shouldn't this kind of thing go to
这种事情不应该去吗
the side of the scale that's favored?
天平的哪一边受到青睐？
I am the scale now.
我现在就是秤了。
Is that really a thing?
这真的是一件事吗？
Yes.
是的。
Can Guo Xu make the decision?
郭旭能做出决定吗？
Is Guo Xu already part of the director's team?
郭旭已经加入导演组了吗？
Let's go.
我们走吧。
It's fine, no problem.
没关系，没问题。
Even if there's no official approval,
即使没有官方批准，
I'll take it as approved, okay?
我就视为批准了，好吗？
Okay.
好的。
Wu Yi, would you like to go on a date with me?
妩衣，你愿意和我约会吗？
Okay
好的
Alright
好吧
Now, dating on our island
现在，在我们的岛上约会
is the same as outside the island
和岛外一样
Congratulations to Zheng Dedong and Weng Fanxi on their successful date
恭喜郑德东和翁凡西约会成功
Alright, now we're at our first check-in point.
好的，现在我们到了第一个登记点。
Come on
快点
Come on, Zheng Dedong
Come on, Zheng Dedong
Come on, let's swing
来吧，我们一起摇摆
Come on
快点
Hurry
匆忙
Actually, I kind of expected it
其实我有点期待
Because I was thinking
因为我在想
Why would someone like Fu Jie want to build a swing?
付洁这样的人为什么要建秋千？
It's like "an iron tree blooming"
就像“铁树开花”
It felt a bit strange
感觉有点奇怪
But I never expected
但我万万没想到
It was a surprise prepared for me and Zheng Dedong
这是为我和郑德东准备的惊喜
I was truly surprised
我真的很惊讶
What?
什么？
You told me Fu Jie wanted to swing?
你告诉我付洁想荡秋千？
I mean, Fu Jie
I mean, Fu Jie
Fu Jie swinging
Fu Jie swinging
"Zhang Fei doing embroidery" (rough exterior but careful inside), you know?
“张飞绣花”（外表粗犷，内心细心）你知道吗？
Guo Xu must have planned it carefully
郭旭肯定是精心策划的
I think he put a lot of thought into it
我认为他花了很多心思
He told me
他告诉我
I could invite
我可以邀请
the female guest I like to swing together
我喜欢一起荡秋千的女嘉宾
I was quite touched
我很感动
Right
正确的
Now let's welcome
现在让我们欢迎
Thank you
谢谢
Let me get the ball for you
让我为你接球
Come on
快点
The sea breeze
海风
The rain under the eaves
屋檐下的雨
After all this time, I still like you the same
过了这么久，我还是一样喜欢你
I'll give you all my best memories
我会给你我所有最美好的回忆
The sea breeze
海风
The rain under the eaves
屋檐下的雨
Swing higher
摆得更高
Zheng Dedong is so shy
Zheng Dedong is so shy
Zheng Dedong, don't be shy
Zheng Dedong, don't be shy
How about this - you push me instead
这样怎么样——你来推我吧
Okay, I'll push you
好吧，我推你一下
Sit more in the center, okay
坐到中间多一点就可以了
Slow down
减速
Okay, I'll push you
好吧，我推你一下
Hold on tight
紧紧抓住
Zheng Dedong
Zheng Dedong
That's our second date spot over there
那是我们第二次约会的地方
I'll leave it to you later
稍后我会把它留给你
There are many little surprises prepared for you
为你准备了很多小惊喜
Show your best, get ready
展现你最好的一面，做好准备
Don't swing too high
不要挥得太高
We'll leave the place to you, we're going first
我们把地方留给你了，我们先走了
I'm speechless
我无语了
I'm truly impressed by them
我对他们印象深刻
You've worked hard
你辛苦了
So this swing was you...
所以这个秋千是你...
Yes, we built it together
是的，我们一起建造的
You built it together?
你们一起建的吗？
Right
正确的
Built it together here
在这里一起建造
I was reluctant at first
一开始我很不情愿
I wondered why we needed this
我想知道为什么我们需要这个
It was Guo Xu's idea
这是郭旭的主意
Yes, Guo Xu suggested it
是的，郭旭建议的
Guo Xu and Jiang Shangru planned it
郭旭和姜尚儒策划的
It's actually quite comfortable
其实还是蛮舒服的
Alright
好吧
Do you get social anxiety?
你有社交恐惧症吗？
I feel like I've become completely introverted
我感觉我变得完全内向了
They really worked hard
他们真的很努力
Yes, very thoughtful
是的，很周到
Be careful
当心
You can go higher
你可以走得更高
Okay
好的
Perfect
完美的
Earlier when they were here
早些时候他们在这里的时候
They must have recorded me
他们一定录了我
Making faces while building the swing
挥杆时做鬼脸
Fu Jie wasn't happy
付洁不高兴了
Let Fu Jie go home
让付洁回家
With these conditions, don't expect too much
有了这些条件，就不要抱太大期望
Why were you making faces?
你为什么做鬼脸？
Because I thought building it this way
因为我想这样构建它
Might not be safe
可能不安全
I was worried since Fu Jie is quite heavy
我很担心付洁太重了
And Lu Wanfei is a girl
而且陆婉菲是个女孩
It wouldn't be good if there was danger
万一有危险就不好了
So where's our next date location?
那么我们下一个约会地点在哪里呢？
They arranged it
他们安排了
I don't know
我不知道
He didn't tell me
他没有告诉我
He didn't tell you?
他没告诉你？
Didn't tell me
没有告诉我
Guo Xu made the arrangements
郭旭做了安排
Slow down
减速
Over there
在那边
I think we should settle
我想我们应该解决
the score with Zheng Dedong once and for all.
与郑德东的比分一劳永逸。
Right.
正确的。
And let me tell you, she's hilarious.
让我告诉你，她很搞笑。
She came looking for me over there.
她到那边来找我了。
Zheng Dedong was right there.
郑德东就在那里。
She's here, what should we do now?
她来了，我们现在该怎么办？
Should we restrain Weng Fanxi now?
现在是不是应该约束翁凡西呢？
Don't let Weng Fanxi find out.
别让翁凡西发现。
His expression was completely stunned at that moment.
那一刻，他的表情彻底错愕了。
My expression...
我的表情...
Let's go back.
我们回去吧。
Yeah, back then Daniel and I
是的，那时丹尼尔和我
just stared at each other, too scared to move.
只是互相盯着对方，吓得不敢动弹。
were completely stunned.
完全惊呆了。
You did great, here's your reward.
你做得很好，这是你的奖励。
Reward? Not this one.
报酬？不是这个。
Heart gesture for you.
为你做的心形手势。
I'll give you a punch instead.
我反而给你一拳。
I'll go wake Chen Menger up for dinner.
我去叫陈梦儿起床吃饭。
Then take the small fan inside with you.
然后把小风扇带进去。
Okay.
好的。
Finally time to eat!
终于到吃饭时间了！
Take it easy
别紧张
Slow down
减速
Really?
真的吗？
They're flowers.
它们是花。
Would you like to give them to me?
你愿意把它们给我吗？
Okay, I'll hand them to you.
好的，我会把它们交给你。
Here.
这里。
Thank them for preparing these for us.
感谢他们为我们准备了这些。
For you.
为你。
This is for you.
这是给您的。
Can't we say you prepared these for me?
难道不能说这些是你为我准备的吗？
Sure.
当然。
If you were preparing them for me,
如果你为我准备的话
what flowers would you choose?
你会选择什么花？
I probably wouldn't choose pink wrapping paper.
我可能不会选择粉红色的包装纸。
I'd choose white wrapping paper.
我会选择白色包装纸。
That way there's a
这样就有一个
better coordination.
更好的协调。
Let me tell you my favorite flower.
让我告诉你我最喜欢的花。
I love lilies the most.
我最喜欢百合了。
Lilies.
百合花。
Okay.
好的。
Then we'll prepare lilies.
然后我们就准备百合花。
Great, thank you.
太好了，谢谢。
Have a seat.
请坐。
Do you like them?
你喜欢他们吗？
I do.
我愿意。
Thank you.
谢谢。
I'm glad you like them.
我很高兴你喜欢它们。
Thank you, Guo Xu.
Thank you, Guo Xu.
Have some fruit.
吃点水果吧
Okay.
好的。
Here's a fork for you.
这是给你的叉子。
I think we're all the type who
我想我们都是这样的类型
when doing certain things
当做某些事情时
if someone we like is nearby
如果我们喜欢的人在附近
we become very nervous
我们变得非常紧张
Right
正确的
When the person you like is around
当喜欢的人在身边时
you appear somewhat
你显得有点
awkward
尴尬的
Yeah
是的
clumsy
笨拙
Exactly
确切地
And just now you saw how
刚才你看到了如何
they were discussing below
他们在下面讨论
Zheng Dedong was super nervous
Zheng Dedong was super nervous
Super what?
超级什么？
Super fake
超级假
Extremely nervous
极度紧张
Yes, I was nervous
是的，我很紧张
Did your ex ever watch you play ball?
你的前任看过你打球吗？
Yes, she did
是的，她做到了
But
但
That day I was both nervous and anxious
那天我既紧张又焦虑
And then I lost
然后我就输了
Right
正确的
But you won today
但今天你赢了
Yes, I won today
是的，今天我赢了
Maybe because it's different people today
也许是因为今天的人不同
Are you feeling better today?
今天你感觉好些了吗？
I've always been fine.
我一直都很好。
Were you feeling a bit off yesterday?
昨天你感觉有点不舒服吗？
A little, because of regret.
有一点，因为遗憾。
I couldn’t take you out to have some fun.
我不能带你出去玩。
Because you really wanted to go out.
因为你真的很想出去。
And we kept losing when we were on the same team.
当我们在同一支球队时，我们总是输球。
I felt a bit embarrassed.
我感到有点尴尬。
Yet you still kept choosing me.
可你还是坚持选择了我。
That’s why I felt a little regretful, yeah.
所以我觉得有点遗憾，是的。
It’s okay.
没关系。
I think I like staying on the island now.
我想我现在喜欢呆在岛上。
If it’s the last day,
如果是最后一天的话
I’d like to chat and spend more time with everyone.
我想和大家聊天，花更多的时间。
Yeah.
是的。
And with you.
和你在一起。
It's a shame I couldn't take you out somewhere fun
可惜没能带你去好玩的地方
Beautiful
美丽的
Sorry about that
对此感到抱歉
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
I'm fine
我很好
You should chat more with everyone and spend time together
你应该多和大家聊天，花时间在一起
And with you too
也和你在一起
I remember when I first entered the venue
记得第一次进场的时候
you were sitting right next to me
你就坐在我旁边
Yes, you sat on my right side
是的，你坐在我的右边
My first impression of you was quite friendly
我对你的第一印象很友好
"Local guy"
“本地人”
You were actually dressed quite flashy that day
那天你其实穿得很花哨
Gaudy
艳俗
Flashy
华而不实
Really?
真的吗？
From what I remember, your outfit was somewhat
据我记忆，你的着装有点
tropical island style
热带岛屿风格
No
不
Wasn't it?
不是吗？
Yes
是的
Weren't you wearing something red
你不是穿了红色的衣服吗
No
不
With some red floral patterns?
有一些红色的花卉图案吗？
What were you wearing on the first day?
第一天穿什么？
I wore all black on the first day
第一天我穿了一身黑
Completely black outfit
全黑装
With some small golden prints
带有一些金色的小印花
Like that
像这样
But nothing red
但没有什么红色的
Then I must have remembered wrong, sorry
那我肯定记错了，抱歉
Anyway when I sat next to you
无论如何，当我坐在你旁边时
I was quite nervous when you first sat down
当你第一次坐下时我很紧张
It's just that
只是这样
You're quite tall
你长得很高
And very beautiful
而且非常漂亮
I was quite nervous when you sat down
当你坐下时我很紧张
But when you started talking to me
但当你开始跟我说话时
I felt
我感觉
less nervous
不那么紧张
You're very approachable
你很平易近人
Right
正确的
You are
你是
I think it's just
我认为这只是
Talking to you feels very familiar
和你说话感觉很熟悉
Because our hometowns are close
因为我们的家乡很近
Yes, it instantly relaxed me
是的，它立刻让我放松了
Right
正确的
You're barely sweating
你几乎不出汗
Yeah
是的
Because you're from Hainan, right?
因为你是海南人，对吧？
Yes
我想我也处理得很好
I'm from Guangdong—I can take the heat
我是广东人——我能忍受炎热
It makes me feel like
这让我感觉
Maybe I can spend more time with you
也许我可以花更多的时间和你在一起
Then I noticed you've been getting pretty close to Chen Guanyu
然后我发现你和陈冠宇走得很近
To be honest
说实话
When you saved Chen Guanyu, I felt a tiny bit
当你救陈冠宇的时候，我有一点感觉
Just a tiny bit
只是一点点
A tiny bit of what?
一点点什么？
A tiny bit like wanting to go home
有点想回家
Weren't you just saying it was a little disappointment?
你刚才不是说有点失望吗？
Just a little disappointment
只是有点失望
Feeling a little disappointed
感觉有点失望
But then again
但话又说回来
It makes perfect sense
这很有道理
That's what you deserve, okay?
这就是你应得的，好吗？
Chen Guanyu asked me out for a walk on the very first day
第一天陈冠宇约我出去散步
On the second day, he wrote me a love letter
第二天，他给我写了一封情书
In the morning
在早晨
You were there
你在那里
You were just idling around your tent
你只是在你的帐篷周围闲逛
Reading books
看书
"Lazybones"
“懒骨头”
Well then
那么好吧
There's really nothing that can be done
实在是无能为力
No wonder those days felt so long
难怪那些日子感觉那么漫长
There was a reason
这是有原因的
Quite comfortable
相当舒服
But we'll be leaving tomorrow
但我们明天就要离开
We'll have to part ways tomorrow
明天我们就得分别了
You seem hesitant to speak.
你似乎在犹豫要不要说话。
How did you know?
你怎么知道的？
I know.
我知道。
Then say something.
然后说点什么。
I still wish the time could be longer
我还是希望时间可以更长一点
When it comes, I want it to end quickly
当它来临的时候，我希望它快点结束
But before leaving, I don't want it to end
但在离开之前我不想结束
But before I came here
但在我来到这里之前
I never imagined it would be like this
我从没想过会是这样
Me neither, not at all
我也不是，一点也不
I feel like I am
我觉得我就是
The matchmaker himself
媒人本人
Plus being an islander
再加上身为岛民
Arranging things for everyone here
在这里为大家安排好事情
To have a good vacation here
来这里度过一个愉快的假期
And have fun, that's all
并且玩得开心，仅此而已
It's rare to have this opportunity
难得有这样的机会
To meet everyone
来跟大家见面
So let's make more friends
所以让我们结交更多的朋友
But most importantly
但最重要的是
I got to know you
我认识你了
I'm quite surprised that I still recognize you.
我很惊讶我还能认出你。
I think it's quite remarkable given your personality.
考虑到你的个性，我认为这是相当了不起的。
It's just that...
只是那...
Here, you've actually become quite straightforward.
到这里，你其实已经变得相当简单了。
I think I have...
我想我有...
I have changed somewhat.
我有些改变了。
You've become...
你已经成为...
More direct in expressing your (thoughts).
更直接地表达你的（想法）。
I think during these days we've spent together...
我想这些天我们是一起度过的...
I feel like every day I've...
我感觉我每天都...
Gotten to know you a little better.
对你更了解一些了。
Every single day...
每一天...
It's been a gradual understanding.
这是一个逐渐的了解。
But...
但...
I feel like today is different again.
我感觉今天又不一样了。
Maybe there's some sadness about parting mixed in.
也许夹杂着一些离别的悲伤。
I'm not sure.
我不知道。
But what I am sure of is...
但我确信的是...
I think I've...
我想我已经...
Fallen for you.
为你倾倒。
I think I've fallen for you.
我想我已经爱上你了。
I think I'm falling for you
我想我爱上你了
I know
我知道
I think I've fallen for you
我想我已经爱上你了
Hello everyone, I'm Weng Fanxi.
大家好，我是翁凡熙。
You can also call me Banban.
你也可以叫我班班。
My first impression of Weng Fanxi
我对翁凡西的第一印象
was that she seemed poised and elegant.
是她看起来泰然自若、优雅。
With a classical charm,
带着古典韵味，
who could resist Weng Fanxi?
谁能抗拒翁凡西？
Once I realized
一旦我意识到
she was the person I most wanted to understand,
她是我最想了解的人
Every day after that when we interacted
之后的每一天我们互动的时候
I never held back
我从不退缩
in expressing how much I liked her
表达我有多喜欢她
This coconut has no water
这个椰子没有水
Rock, paper, scissors
石头、剪刀、布
Would you ever bet everything on me?
你愿意把一切都押在我身上吗？
I would
我会
He's getting closer
他越来越近了
Is it tasty?
好吃吗？
Today, he was very direct with me
今天他对我很直接
In our past conversations
在我们过去的谈话中
he never actually mentioned it
他实际上从未提到过
To express your feelings so directly
如此直接地表达自己的感受
So I was pleasantly surprised today
所以今天我很惊喜
Let's go
我们走吧
Okay
好的
Is yours okay?
你的还好吗？
It's fine
没关系
Let's go
我们走吧
Take this to thank them
拿这个来感谢他们
The feeling of parting is coming soon
离别的感觉即将来临
It ends tomorrow
明天结束
I really don't want to talk about this
我真的不想谈论这个
I wanted to say it earlier but couldn't bring myself to
我本来想早点说，但没能说出口
I'm feeling complicated now
我现在心情很复杂
Tonight will be a sleepless night, I'm telling you
今晚将是一个不眠之夜，我告诉你
Really
真的
Absolutely won't sleep
绝对睡不着
I don't even feel like sleeping
我什至不想睡觉
Who do you think I'll choose tomorrow?
你觉得我明天会选择谁？
I might choose quite a few
我可能会选择不少
Why did you...
你为什么...
No
不
Are you together?
你们在一起吗？
I like Weng Fanxi
I like Weng Fanxi
Does it make your heart flutter?
是不是让你心动不已？